freeblogspot.org 2012-06-30

# Privacy policy | Create a free Blog Free Blogs Websites Blogging Sites

FreeBlogSpot.org privacy policy

FreeBlogSpot.org is an Internet blogging site that allows its users to set up individual, personal blogs that can be shared and viewed by networks of friends and family. FreeBlogSpot.org bloggers can view each other’s blogs and correspond with other bloggers throughout the site. Users can post their ideas, photos, videos, diaries, experiences, various comments, and describe their interests through blogs. FreeBlogSpot.org users can modify their personal information at any time and have the ability to manage how other FreeBlogSpot.org users and the service communicates with them. FreeBlogSpot.org has its blogging users’ best interests in mind regarding their privacy and security. Should you feel that you have any questions regarding the FreeBlogSpot.org policy on privacy, please feel free to contact us.  
Personal information we may collect

FreeBlogSpot.org may gather personal information when you register for your blogging membership, service, or otherwise willingly provide such personal information. FreeBlogSpot.org may store personal information collected from you with information from other FreeBlogSpot.org services or perhaps third parties in order to provide improved user know-how, including customizing content for our members.

FreeBlogSpot.org may utilize cookies and other technology to improve your Internet blogging experience and to study how you use FreeBlogSpot.org in order to make progressive changes to the quality of our services we provide in the future. FreeBlogSpot.org servers, by design, record information when you visit our blogging site or when you use some of the products designed by FreeBlogSpot.org. This may include the IP address, URL, browser type, language, and the date and time of your application.

Your options

Whenever possible, FreeBlogSpot.org provides its users with choices when we ask for personal information. You have the right to refuse entering your personal information to us and/or reject cookies in your computer’s browser; however, some of our features or services at FreeBlogSpot.org may not be able to work for you if you choose to decline them. Here at FreeBlogSpot.org, we strive to provide our users with the best possible Internet services, and we work hard to provide our bloggers access to their personal information when they request it. We work diligently to provide our users the chance to update such data if it is incorrect and delete it when realistically possible to do so.  
How we may use your information

At times, FreeBlogSpot.org may utilize personal information to provide the services you have asked for. This may include services that display customized blogging content and advertising.

Additionally, we may also utilize the personal information you voluntarily provide for review to do research with or in order to operate and improve our services for the FreeBlogSpot.org blogging community. We may share grouped non-personal information from your registration as a whole, or part, with third parties outside of FreeBlogSpot.org for research and other statistical uses.

Should FreeBlogSpot.org use third parties to support us in processing your personal information, we oblige them to use the same privacy conditions that we do at FreeBlogSpot.org at the minimum. They must comply with our privacy policy principals and any other suitable privacy and safekeeping procedures.

FreeBlogSpot.org may share information with third parties in limited conditions, including when complying with legal procedures, preventing fraud or impending harm, and ensuring the protection of our network of bloggers and services. FreeBlogSpot.org processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America as well as other countries and principalities. In addition to this, FreeBlogSpot.org processes personal information on a server outside your own country of residence.

Promotions, contests and giveaways

Occasionally, FreeBlogSpot.org sponsors contests. Users wishing to take part in these giveaways and other promotions may be asked to provide FreeBlogSpot.org with personal information including name, age, home address, phone contact and email address or to answer questions in order to take part in such contests. Rarely, but in some instances, FreeBlogSpot.org may need to transfer a user’s personal information to certain advertising partners that you have openly requested to obtain information from. It will be obvious at the point of compilation who is collecting the user’s personal information and whose privacy statement will be relevant.  
Additional disclosures

Any personal information voluntarily entered to any blog at FreeBlogSpot.org, including user videos and photos and any other personal identification information that is displayed publicly to people in order to assist user communication in the FreeBlogSpot.org blogging community is done so, completely at the user’s discretion. FreeBlogSpot.org may use its user’s email address to send updates and other types of communications to its users. Users may choose not to take delivery of these emails by electing to do so upon registration.

All FreeBlogSpot.org bloggers and users must fully understand that whenever they willingly post public information to blogs or any other public forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.  
Links

FreeBlogSpot.org may contain links to outside sites. FreeBlogSpot.org is not accountable for the privacy policies, content, and/or situations on other Internet sites. When linking to another site, bloggers will want to be certain that they are fully aware of that site’s privacy policies and practices. The FreeBlogSpot.org privacy policy only applies to information collected on FreeBlogSpot.org itself.  
Privacy policy updates or other changes

As FreeBlogSpot.org progresses, or situations in development arise, changes to our privacy policy may come about. Should changes be made, we will post them in complete form on our site to make FreeBlogSpot.org users conscious of what the changes are. This will allow the FreeBlogSpot.org community to continually become aware of what information FreeBlogSpot.org collects, how it is used, and when it would be disclosed. All FreeBlogSpot.org bloggers and users are bound by any minor changes to the policy when they use the site after those changes have been posted. What’s more, if we are going to use users’ individually identifiable information in a method considerably different from what is stated at the time of compilation, we will notify by posting a notice on our website for an adequate amount of time or through email communications.
